Inventory of the James A. Bill Papers 1940-2003
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
- Collection of Iranian Information, 1963-1993, bulk 1980-1991
  - Information on Iran including the Iran-Contra; Early 1990s (1)
    - (1, 8)
      - Interviews (1, 8, 6)
        - (1, 8, 6, 7)
          - Interview of Hubert Humphrey by Joe B. Frantz, Given on 8/17/1971 (1, 8, 6, 7)
          - Interview of W. Averill Harriman, donated to the Lyndon Baines Johnson Library, 2/4/1972 (1, 8, 6, 7)
        Subseries 7: Correspondence with Bill
      - Correspondence with Bill (1, 8, 7)
        - (1, 8, 7)
            Series 1: Letter to Bill from Fereidun Fesharaki, 2/13/1981, regards to a paper on World Oil availability
          - Letter to Bill from Fereidun Fesharaki, 2/13/1981, regards to a paper on World Oil availability (1, 8, 7)
            Series 2: Letter from Bill to Bill Paul, follow up from phone conversation, 8/12/1986
          - Letter from Bill to Bill Paul, follow up from phone conversation, 8/12/1986 (1, 8, 7)
            Series 3: Letter from Bill to John Macy, regards to setting up a meeting, 8/21/1983
          - Letter from Bill to John Macy, regards to setting up a meeting, 8/21/1983 (1, 8, 7)
            Series 4: Letter to Bill from Max [?], regards to identification of those working against Helms, 9/16/1986
          - Letter to Bill from Max [?], regards to identification of those working against Helms, 9/16/1986 (1, 8, 7)
            Series 5: Letter from Bill to Michael [?], regards to obtaining the address of Mark Lytle, etc, 3/3/1989
          - Letter from Bill to Michael [?], regards to obtaining the address of Mark Lytle, etc, 3/3/1989 (1, 8, 7)
        Subseries 8: Government Documents (copies)
      - Government Documents (copies) (1, 8)
        - (1, 8, 9)
          - Ayatollah Shirazi Discusses Limits to Clerical Rule, translation from German, 2/16/1981 (1, 8, 9)
          - Information from a session of the Supreme Defense Council in the presence of Imam Khomeyni, 8/17/1981 (1, 8, 9)
          - A copy of a press release, Uncovered Assassination Plot, published in Tehran on 12/24/1970, attached is a handwritten note to Bill, unsigned (1, 8, 9)
          - Document regarding the Foreign Factors and Influences, with a focus on US Military assistance programs, marked For Official Use Only, n.d. (1, 8, 9)
        Subseries 9: Personal Notes
      - Personal Notes (1, 8, 9)
        - (1, 8, 9, 10)
          - Information on "Citing Historical Materials" (1, 8, 9, 10)
          - Various To-Do lists of people to call and/or write, notes to self (1, 8, 9, 10)
          - List of Iranian related materials (1, 8, 9, 10)
        Subseries 10: Notes on working texts
      - Notes on working texts (1, 8, 10)
        - Three notebooks and a legal size piece of paper with notes on texts in progress (1, 8, 10, 11)
        Subseries 11: Full Texts
      - Full Texts (1, 8, 11)
        - A copy of United States Army Special Warfare School: A Survey of the Tribes of Iran, Capt. Robert Hand, 7/22/1963 (1, 8, 11, 12)
        Subseries 12: Notes and Articles on Iran, Middle East Production, And Minerals
      - Notes and Articles on Iran, Middle East Production, And Minerals (1, 8, 12)
        - (1, 8, 12, 13)
          - Notes on Iranian construction, costs, etc. (1, 8, 12, 13)
        - Middle East producers of copper, lead, zinc, nickel (1, 8, 12, 14)
          - Morocco closes grip on phosphate market Kayhan International, 8/17/1976 (1, 8, 12, 14)
          - US red tape hampers huge Algeria gas sales Kayhan International, 1/26/1977 (1, 8, 12, 14)
          - Egypt oil output may hit 1m. barrels in 1980 Kayhan International, 2/3/1977 (1, 8, 12, 14)
          - Arabs boost Jordan potash mine venture Kayhan International, 3/26/1977 (1, 8, 12, 14)
          - Copper resources may top 850m. tons, Kayhan International, 7/11/1977 (1, 8, 12, 14)
          - N. Yemen makes big copper discovery Kayhan International, 8/24/1977 (1, 8, 12, 14)
          - Phosphate mining: more than ecology, food at stake The Christian Science Monitor, 8/30/1977 (1, 8, 12, 14)
          - Rabat in phosphate talks, Kayhan International, 10/9/1977 (1, 8, 12, 14)
          - Iran gets copper group bid Kayhan International, 10/10/1977 (1, 8, 12, 14)
          - Huge uranium deposit found in Black Sea, Kayhan International, 11/1/1977 (1, 8, 12, 14)
          - Black Sea uranium unviable Kayhan International, 11/2/1977 (1, 8, 12, 14)
          - Egypt oil search is a gamble Kayhan International, 11/6/1977 (1, 8, 12, 14)
          - Iran seventh big copper producer Kayhan International, n.d.; attached notes (1, 8, 12, 14)
          - Rabat set to sign deal of century Kayhan International, 11/13/1977 (1, 8, 12, 14)
          - Copper finds lift hopes for other minerals, The Times, 11/17/1977 (1, 8, 12, 14)
          - Paper: Mineral Resources of the Middle East by Soraya Diase, 12/2/1977, Professor Bill student (1, 8, 12, 14)
          - Gold reportedly found in Saudi Arabia, CSM, 1/19/1978 (1, 8, 12, 14)
          - $9,000 million phosphate deal aims at 30 years co-operation, MEED, 2/10/1978, vol. 22, no. 6 (1, 8, 12, 14)
          - Morocco Development Report, 2-3/1978, vol. 1, no. 1 (1, 8, 12, 14)
          - Soviet strength in oil, uranium: CIA debate, and a N. Africa deal, 3/10/1978 (1, 8, 12, 14)
          - Articles from Economic Intelligence, 6/30/1978 (1, 8, 12, 14)
          - Arab gas exports under fire, Kayhan International, 7/4/1978 (1, 8, 12, 14)
          - N. Yemen in big oil strike, Kayhan International, 9/2/1978 (1, 8, 12, 14)
          - Lodes of uranium ore in Algeria 8/9/1980 (1, 8, 12, 14)
          - Mauritania drive on minerals 9/27/1980 (1, 8, 12, 14)
          - First Oil, now minerals; US frets at import growth, Christian Science Monitor, 10/2/1980 (1, 8, 12, 14)
          - Hot US Intelligence expert joins CIA, Christian Science Monitor, 1/29/1981 (1, 8, 12, 14)
          - New offshore discoveries make US phosphate-rich, Christian Science Monitor, 2/25/1981 (1, 8, 12, 14)
          - Strategic Minerals Are center of new east-west war, The Rising Tide, 5/1981 (1, 8, 12, 14)
          - Rust in system could turn arms buildup into a big backlog, The Christian Science Monitor, 5/27/1981 (1, 8, 12, 14)
          - In Saudi Arabia, another search for The other minerals, Aramco World Magazine, 7-8/1981 (1, 8, 12, 14)
          - Major Oil Finds seen likely in mideast, Africa, The Wall Street Journal, 11/23/1981 (1, 8, 12, 14)
        - (1, 8, 12, 15)
            Subseries 1: Articles from Industrial Minerals
          - Articles from Industrial Minerals (1, 8, 12, 15)
            - Granges assists phosphate project 10/1976 (1, 8, 12, 15)
            - German help on phosphates, 10/1976 (1, 8, 12, 15)
            - Phosphate: Who for Bu Craa? 2/1976 (1, 8, 12, 15)
            - Bromine and phosphate for Europe, 3/1976 (1, 8, 12, 15)
            - "Bu Craa tug-of-war", 3/1976 (1, 8, 12, 15)
            - 10,000m. tons of phosphate?, 4/1976 (1, 8, 12, 15)
            - Phosphate oversupply despite fertilizer upturn, 7/1976 (1, 8, 12, 15)
            - The world phosphate rock institute programme, 1/1976 (1, 8, 12, 15)
            - Phosphate market continues weak, 12/1975 (1, 8, 12, 15)
            - Phosphate rock trade levels, 11/1975 (1, 8, 12, 15)
            - Ambitious phosphate plans, 7/1975 (1, 8, 12, 15)
            - Phosphate and potash expansion, 4/1975 (1, 8, 12, 15)
            - World Phosphate rock institute off the ground, 3/1975 (1, 8, 12, 15)
            - Phosphate market - boom, vacillation & recovery, 11/1976 (1, 8, 12, 15)
            - World phosphate producers, 11/1976 (1, 8, 12, 15)
            - Phosphate see-saw, 2/1976 (1, 8, 12, 15)
            - Governments and resources, 4/1975 (1, 8, 12, 15)
            - 1975 and all that, 1/1975 (1, 8, 12, 15)
            - Phosphate forecasts, 3/1975 (1, 8, 12, 15)
            Subseries 2: Notes on phosphates
          - Notes on phosphates (1, 8, 12, 15, 2)
            - Phosphate rock The Commodity Data Summaries, 1/1976 with handwritten notes on US imports of phosphates (1, 8, 12, 15, 2)
            - Reported reserves of phosphate rock (1, 8, 12, 15, 2)
            - Leading world producers of phosphate rock Mineral Yearbook, vol. III, 1974, p 54 (1, 8, 12, 15, 2)
            - Handwritten notes on Oil in Sinai ME International, 2/1974, p. 22 (1, 8, 12, 15, 2)
            - Phosphate windfall enriches Arabs 8 days, 1/24/19? (1, 8, 12, 15, 2)
            - Afghanistan unsung riches by John Shroder, n.d. (1, 8, 12, 15, 2)
            - Exploiting Afganistan Foreign Report, 2/4/1982, no. 1714 (1, 8, 12, 15, 2)
    Subseries 2: Iran Contra
  - Iran Contra (2)
    - (2, 8)
        Subseries 1: Iran Contra Information
      - Iran Contra Information (2, 8, 1)
          Subseries 1: Articles and Newspaper clippings
        - Articles and Newspaper clippings (2, 8, 1)
            Subseries 1: Articles and clippings from 1986
          - Articles and clippings from 1986 (2, 8, 1)
            - List of articles entitled Events on November 1986 US Policy towards Iran (2, 8, 1, 16)
              - Peres approved idea of Israel as middleman in US-Iran deals, The Jerusalem Post, 11/10/1986 (2, 8, 1, 16)
              - Israeli reportedly set up first US-Iran arms deal, The Washington Post, 11/19/1986 (2, 8, 1, 16)
              - By Reagan About Iran, New York Times, 11/14/1986 (2, 8, 1, 16)
              - CIA Curried favor with Khomeini, Exiles, The Washington Post, 11/19/1986 (2, 8, 1, 16)
              - Iran Says McFarlane tapes show lie, New York Times, 11/29/1986 (2, 8, 1, 16)
              - US Employed a sting setup for arms to Iran, New York Times, 11/29/1986 (2, 8, 1, 16)
              - Israeli sale said allowed by Haig in 81 The Washington Post on 11/29/1986 (2, 8, 1, 16)
              - Paper: Arms package worth $1 Billion, The Huntsville Times 11/30/1986 (2, 8, 1, 16)
              - Mystery man at the centre of Iran arms web, The Observer, 11/30/1986 (2, 8, 1, 16)
              - London house was HQ for Iran arms deal:, The Sunday Times, 11/30/1986 (2, 8, 1, 16)
              - Evidence points to big Saudi role in Iranian and Contra Arms Deals New York Times, 11/30/19? (2, 8, 1, 16)
              - Day by Day: The US Account of the Investigation, New York Times, 11/30/1986 (2, 8, 1, 16)
              - Colonel North Lives, New York Times, 11/30/1986 (2, 8, 1, 16)
              - Transcript of Reagan remarks to his investigative panel, New York Times, 12/2/1986 (2, 8, 1, 16)
              - What the president did not know?, The Christian Science Monitor, 12/3/1986 (2, 8, 1, 16)
              - Israel: America Middleman? Washington Weekly, 12/4/1986 (2, 8, 1, 16)
              - Spotlight focusing on retired air force general, New Analysis, 12/5/1986 (2, 8, 1, 16)
              - The Story so far, New York Times, 12/14/1986 (2, 8, 1, 16)
              - Iran testimony conflicts, The Christian Science Monitor, 12/19/1986 (2, 8, 1, 16)
              - Beirut Rag The Nation, 12/20/1986 (2, 8, 1, 16)
              - Wider Saudi role in Iran deal hinted The Baltimore Sun, 12/22/1986 (2, 8, 1, 16)
              - Outside Experts on Iran Consulted by staff of New Security Adviser, New York Times, 12/28/1986 (2, 8, 1, 16)
              - North probe to steer away from Israel pot, AAS, 12/31/1986 (2, 8, 1, 16)
            Subseries 2: Articles and clippings from 1987
          - Articles and clippings from 1987 (2, 8, 1)
            - (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - Kimche denies advance knowledge of contra, The Washington Jewish Weekly, 1/8/1987 (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - Israeli officials may testify before Senate, The Jerusalem Post, 1/9/1987 (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - Contra Diversion plan originated with Israeli, Senate committee told, Washington Post, 1/10/1897 (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - McFarlane took cake and bible to Teheran, Ex-CIA man says, New York Times, 1/11/1987 (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - Israel convinced US to take initiative, The Jerusalem Post, 1/11/1987 (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - Israelis dismiss suggestion they led US into Iran dealings, New York Times, 1/12/1987 (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - Israel necessary connection to Iran, Washington Jewish Week, 1/18/1987 (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - Fraying strands loosen US-Israel love knot, Washington Jewish Week, 1/18/1987 (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - False US tips led to a defeat in 1986, Iraq says, New York Times, 1/19/1987 (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - Senate report says administration ignored warning to pitfalls in arms sales to Iran, New York Times, 1/19/1987 (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - Iran arms principal admitted payoffs, The Baltimore Sun, 1/19/1987 (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - What Ollie North told me before he took the fifth, National Review, 1/30/1987 (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - Contras are the focus of 7 investigations, New York Times, 1/30/1987 (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - Report of Senate select panel: establishing a sequence of Iran arms events, New York Times, 2/1/1987 (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - Huge Illegal deal on arms for Iran was known to US: Private sales are traced, New York Times, 2/2/1987 (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - Ledeen seems to relish Iran insider role, The Washington Post, 2/2/1987 (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - Reorganizing the NSC is not enough, The Christian Science Monitor, 2/4/1987 (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - McFarlane is hospitalized for an overdose of Valium, New York Times, 2/10/1987 (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - US hedges on any Israeli hostage deal, The Christian Science Monitor, 2/11/1987 (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - Bush says he expressed reservations to key players on Iran-arms policy, Wall Street Journal, 2/13/1987 (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - A Blockade of Iran, The Wall Street Journal, 2/13/1987 (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - Computer at N.S.C. is said to reveal broad operations, New York Times, 2/14/1987 (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - Casey is termed the mastermind of efforts to supply the Contras, New York Times, 3/25/1987 (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - Purported Iran envoy offered candidate Reagan deal, aides say, San Jose Mercury News, 4/12/1987 (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - Reagan aides reportedly held secret talks on hostages in 80, The Huntsville Times, 4/12/1987 (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - Money trail leads to Secord, San Francisco Examiner, 4/12/1987 (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - The wiles of Teheran, New York Times, 8/3/1987 (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - Walsh, Senate panel want to know why FBI delayed airing Iran arms-sales files, The Wall Street Journal, 4/13/1987 (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - Moslem leader: Hostages stay until Reagan out, Sheik Reported to Link Reagan and Hostages, New York Times, 1/18/1988 (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - Numerous articles on one page: New York Times, 5/9/1987 (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - Courier for North tells of carrying cash for Contras, New York Times, 5/15/1987 (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - Walk back the cat, New York Times, 5/21/1987 (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - Mysterious death of Iranian arms dealer under investigation, San Jose Mercury News, 6/13/1987 (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - Report traces Iran arms deal back to 1980, San Francisco Examiner, 4/25/1987 (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - Minority report, The Nation, 6/20/1987 (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - North allegedly made plan for martial law, Hartford Courant, 7/5/1987 (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - North and the government, San Jose Mercury News, 7/5/1987 (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - October Surprise by Warren Hinckle in San Francisco Examiner, 7/12/1987 (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - Reagan 1980 Hostage Deal, L.A. Weekly, 7/10-16/1987 (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - Arms sellers, Israelis Allege US Tie to early Iran deals, Newsday, 11/22/1987, with a letter to Senator Warren Rudman on the back, dated 7/13/1987 regards to standing up to Ollie North (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - Early arms help to Iran: Israel-Iran arms tie known to CIA in 81, San Jose Mercury, 8/9/1987 (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - Reagan campaign contacts with Iran in 1980 probed, The Miami Herald, 9/28/1987; CIA knew of 1981 of arms deals, The Miami Herald, 8/9/1987 (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - Uncovering details of the Iran-contra covert operations lobby, The Christian Science Monitor, 10/22/1987 (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - Letter to Senator Robert Byrd from Glenn McDuffie in regards to weapons trade with Iran and taking action, dated 10/23/1987, enclosures included (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - Iran report omissions, San Francisco Examiner, 11/20/1987 (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - Israel said to have sold weapons to Iran since 1981 with tacit approval of the Reagan administration, The Wall Street Journal, 11/28/1986 (2, 8, 1, 17)
              - The hidden truth about hostages in Iran, Asbury Park Press, 12/28/1987 (2, 8, 1, 17)
            Subseries 3: Articles and clippings from 1988-1989
          - Articles and clippings from 1988-1989 (2, 8, 1, 3)
            - (2, 8, 1, 3, 18)
              - Former CIA agent running covert campaign for Bush, Examiner?, 2/29/1988 (2, 8, 1, 3, 18)
              - Around Ortega dinner table, Americans talk business, politics, The Christian Science Monitor, 4/7/1988 (2, 8, 1, 3, 18)
              - A rerun of Robber Baron ethics, The Washington Spectator, 6/1/1988 (2, 8, 1, 3, 18)
              - Khomeini still secretly getting US arms, Iranian rebels charge, Los Angeles Times, 6/28/1988 (2, 8, 1, 3, 18)
              - Burning Bush, San Francisco Examiner, 7/31/1988 (2, 8, 1, 3, 18)
              - Ex-aide: Ron made Iran deal in 1980, Daily News, 8/26/1988 (2, 8, 1, 3, 18)
              - The translation of DER Spiegel article on the October surprise, 9/5/1988 (2, 8, 1, 3, 18)
              - Anyone care about the cover-up, San Francisco Examiner, 9/18/1988 (2, 8, 1, 3, 18)
              - Bush link hinted in 1980 hostage talks, San Francisco Examiner, 10/5/1988 (2, 8, 1, 3, 18)
              - A release from the California Democratic Council on Bush-Terrorist-Hostage Investigation Demand, 10/8/1988 (2, 8, 1, 3, 18)
              - Post takes aim at 1980 story, but misses mark; If it October... then it time for an Iranian Conspiracy Theory, 10/9/1988 (2, 8, 1, 3, 18)
              - In These Times, vol. 12, no. 39, 10/12-18/1988 (2, 8, 1, 3, 18)
              - The October Surprise that will not go away, Los Angeles Herald Examiner, 10/13/1988 (2, 8, 1, 3, 18)
              - Did Bush delay hostages release? Times-Standard, Eureka, California, 10/17/1988 (2, 8, 1, 3, 18)
              - Bush and the October Surprise, Oakland Tribune, 10/18/1988 (2, 8, 1, 3, 18)
              - Pre-election hostage release fishy, Charleston (W. Va.) Evening Gazette, 10/19/1988 (2, 8, 1, 3, 18)
              - The issue is treason, Oakland Tribune, 10/19/1988 (2, 8, 1, 3, 18)
              - Reagan-Bush 80 arms deal with Iran charged, Christian Science Monitor, 10/21/1988 (2, 8, 1, 3, 18)
              - Did Reagan, Bush cut a 1980 Hostage deal?, The Boston Globe, 10/23/1988 (2, 8, 1, 3, 18)
              - Full pages of Los Angeles Times, 10/25/1988 (2, 8, 1, 3, 18)
              - Hostage says US is hurting his release, Los Angeles Times, 10/31/1988 (2, 8, 1, 3, 18)
              - Minority Report, The Nation, 11/14/1988 (2, 8, 1, 3, 18)
              - US-Israel Accord said to authorize north-nir operations, The Washington Post, 12/4/1988 (2, 8, 1, 3, 18)
              - Survivor of Mexican crash reportedly used alias, The Washington Post, 12/4/1988 (2, 8, 1, 3, 18)
              - Cover-up Agitprop theories, The Washington Post, 2/4/1989 (2, 8, 1, 3, 18)
              - Hussein visit leaves US Optimistic, The Christian Science Monitor, 4/25/1989 (2, 8, 1, 3, 18)
              - North file fills out a record of bad faith, The Wall Street Journal, 5/10/1989 (2, 8, 1, 3, 18)
            Subseries 4: Articles and clippings from 1990-1991, including trial information related to Iran-Contra Affair
          - Articles and clippings from 1990-1991, including trial information related to Iran-Contra Affair (2, 8, 1, 4)
            - (2, 8, 1, 4, 19)
              - Trial of Poindexter could shed further light on roles of Bush, Reagan in Iran Contra Affair, The Wall Street Journal, 2/13/1990 (2, 8, 1, 4, 19)
              - Reagan, on videotape, pleads ignorance of key parts of the Iran-Contra Affair, The Wall Street Journal, 2/23/1990 (2, 8, 1, 4, 19)
              - Last Laugh, The Washington Post, 2/27/1990 (2, 8, 1, 4, 19)
              - Why Reagan added little to Iran-Contra, New York Times, 3/2/1990 (2, 8, 1, 4, 19)
              - Jurors felt testimony by Reagan irrelevant, The Washington Post, 4/8/1990 (2, 8, 1, 4, 19)
              - Reagan testimony had little impact on decision, Poindexter jurors reportÂ¸ The Washington Post, 4/8/1990 (2, 8, 1, 4, 19)
              - Poindexter convicted of 5 Iran-contra counts, The Washington Post, 4/8/1990 (2, 8, 1, 4, 19)
              - Selected article from New York Times, 4/29/1990 (2, 8, 1, 4, 19)
              - Arms funds reportedly diverted, Daily Press, 4/29/1990 (2, 8, 1, 4, 19)
              - Where George Was, The Washington Post, 6/10/1990 (2, 8, 1, 4, 19)
              - Poindexter gets 6 months in prison over Iran-Contra, New York Times, 6/12/1990 (2, 8, 1, 4, 19)
              - Testimony that Bush was told in 1986 of contra supply scheme, New York Times, 7/30/1990 (2, 8, 1, 4, 19)
              - Ex-CIA agent is convicted in Iran-Contra affair, New York Times, 9/19/1990 (2, 8, 1, 4, 19)
              - New allegations implicate Reagan, Christian Science Monitor, 4/19/1991 (2, 8, 1, 4, 19)
              - Bush had lunch with Potter Stewart, not with Iranians, The Wall Street Journal, 5/8/1991 (2, 8, 1, 4, 19)
              - The First Stone: Agent McFarlane, [?] Times, 5/29-6/11/1991 (2, 8, 1, 4, 19)
              - Secret secrets and open secrets, The Wall Street Journal, 7/3/1991 (2, 8, 1, 4, 19)
              - Iran-contra prosecutors concentrate on a former CIA task force chief, The Washington Post, 7/7/1991 (2, 8, 1, 4, 19)
              - A page of CIA information and articles: New York Times, 7/10/1991 (2, 8, 1, 4, 19)
              - Getting warm on Iran-contra, The Washington Post, 7/16/1991 (2, 8, 1, 4, 19)
              - Gates hearing delayed 2 months, USA Today, 7/17/1991 (2, 8, 1, 4, 19)
            Subseries 5: Articles and clippings from 1992-1993, 1999 including Vice President Bush involvement
          - Articles and clippings from 1992-1993, 1999 including Vice President Bush involvement (2, 8, 1, 5)
            - (2, 8, 1, 5, 20)
              - Cartoon: The Washington Post, Hang tough - only a little while more to go (2, 8, 1, 5, 20)
              - Document from Loiry Publishing House with title of a text: The report of the Vice President involvement in the Iran-contra scandal by William S. Loiry, with where to order the text (2, 8, 1, 5, 20)
              - Did he know? The Washington Post Magazine, 8/16/1992, cover + p. 11-14, 23-32 (2, 8, 1, 5, 20)
              - Reports still link Bush to Iran-contra affair The Christian Science Monitor, 10/8/1992 (2, 8, 1, 5, 20)
              - Clinton for president, The Virginia Gazette, 10/14/1992, mentions Bush involvement with Iran-Contra (2, 8, 1, 5, 20)
              - Bush Bristles at queries on role in Iran Initiative, The Washington Post, 10/14/1992 (2, 8, 1, 5, 20)
              - The president unchanged position on Iran-Contra, The Washington Post, 10/15/1992 (2, 8, 1, 5, 20)
              - Bush didnt know, 10/16/1992 (2, 8, 1, 5, 20)
              - Iran-Contra document says Bush favored secrecy in hostage affair, New York Times, 10/21/1992 (2, 8, 1, 5, 20)